

LYNDON ELLISON TOMAS

Web Developer

Studying to become Full-Stack Web Developer with experience in programming and deploying stand-alone websites alongside professionals. Values quality over quantity, and a solid contributor and facilitator in projects. Aims to apply his knowledge and expertise in Web Development for the improvement of the company's website.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- OJT under R&D team of School of Computing (S.Y. 2018– 2019)
 - o Encoder
 - Data Organizer for Mr. Dave Marcial's studies
- Student Assistant (Academic Scholarship Requirement S.Y. 2019-2020)
 - Encoder (incoming enrollees)
 - Scholar Representative
 - VLT Scholarship Facilitator & Coordinator

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

- iACADEMY (2018-present)
 - Recipient of Academic Excellence Award (GWA 1.221)
 - BGF NxtGen Scholar and Advocate (2019 present)
 - o Academic Scholar (2019-2020)
 - \circ (as of 1st semester of SY. 2020-2021) GWA: 1.1
- Silliman University (2016-2018)
 - o Academic Scholar (G.A. 95.11)
 - o SU SHS Student Council Representative (2016)
 - Everwings: Best Selling Booth (2018)
 - Tech Assistant (SU Dorm Committee)
- Charis School (2010-2016)
 - Tech Assistant for events
 - Graduated as SALUTATORIAN (G.A. 95.209)
 - o Math-Sci Club Member
 - Student Council Member

CONTACT DETAILS

- (02) 8288 4542
- Marikina, NCR
- 201801180@iacademy.edu.ph
- https://www.facebook.com/lyndon.tomas/

SKILLS

LANGUAGES/DIALECTS SPOKEN

Filipino 100%
English 90%
Cebuano 50%

90%

PROGRAMS USED

VS Code

HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap,
JS, Vue, Node, MongoDB,
Java (Eclipse), C++ (Dev-

MS Office 80%

Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Publish, Access

Adobe 70%
Photoshop, Animate,

After Effects, Premiere
Pro, Audition,
Dreamweaver

XAMPP 70% PHP, MySQL 70% 70%

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthday: June 7, 1999

Sex: Male

Place of Birth: QC

Religion: Christianity (Protestant)

Marital Status: Single